Paidamoyo - Janet Azehko

E-Mail Me! LinkedIn GitHub

I am a former circus performer, fashion designer and self taught web developer seeking a career in tech that suits my professional skills, ability to quickly learn new things, and my love of finding creative ways to look at the world. My decade-long career as an artist and performer gives me the unique ability to find creative and empathetic solutions to every problem. I can bring creativity, drive, and passion to your organization.

Education

City College of San Francisco

Associates of Art Fashion Design (Spring 2022)

Academy of Art University

Bachelors of Art Fashion Product Development (TBD)

Skills

Web Development:

Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React

Tools: Visual Studio Code, Git, GitHub, Chrome Developer Tools, NPM, Boostrap, LESS, Node, js, Figma, Adobe Photoshop, Loom

Project Management:

- Scheduling
- Event Production
- Budgeting
- Conflict Management

Experience

Kinfolq

Community Manager 4/2021 - Current

Remote

- Provide engaging text, image and video content for all social media and professional accounts.
- Set plan and implement social media and communication campaigns and strategies.
- Monitor, track and report on feedback and online reviews.
- · Organize and manage events to boost brand awareness and consumer engagement.
- · Respond to members in a timely manner.
- Build relationships with customers, industry professionals and potential members.
- Stay up-to-date with trends in tech and venture capital.

Concept SF Inc

Lead Editor 1/2018- Current

- Review submitted posts and decide which ones to accept and reject.
- Edit posts for clarity, grammar and match for style and tone.
- Write or modify content to maximize post quality, reader interest, and social media referrals.
- Ensure that blog posts go to clients in a timely manner.
- Develop proposals for achieving goals and targets, including increasing readership and content engagement.
- Execute on planned strategies to achieve set targets while ensuring quality remains high. Use metrics and data to measure progress.
- Cultivate and support volunteer contributions to ensure a dependable, diverse group of content creators.
- Lead meetings to plan editorial content for upcomming projects.

1/2 127.0.0.1:5500/index.html

Code Crew

Teacher's Assistant 3/2021 - Current

Memphis, TN (remote)

- Work with lead teacher to monitor class attendance.
- Revise lesson material with students individually or in small groups.
- Collaborate with lead teachers to recognize issues students are facing and recommend solutions.
- Grade student's assignments using online grading system.
- Document student progress and communicate with staff.
- Ensure a safe online learning environment.

Grabango

Quality Trainer 1/2019 - 10/2019

Berkeley, CA

- Helped teams collect, clean and label data and images.
- Identified and categorized objects in images and videos.
- · Annotated actions in images and videos.
- Used various sets of rules to process data sets, logged exceptions as they occurred.

Tech Inclusion

Social Media Volunteer 1/2016 - 10/2019

San Francisco, CA

- Plan and execute social media campaigns for events in New York San Francisco, London, Melbourne and others both nationally and internationally.
- Successfully implemented a new video interview component to Social Media that increased follower engagement.
- Managed social media accounts with over 3,000 followers.

Kinetic Arts Center

Administrative Assistant 6/2018 - 3/2019

Oakland, CA

- · Managed front desk, including telephones, mail/messages, faxes and visitors.
- Reviewed and entered class enrollment into MindBody software system.
- · Registered new clients and assist with purchases of class packages and merchandise.
- · Provided correspondence for customer concerns in person, by phone and email.
- Managed community donations on behalf of Kinetic Arts.

Project Erostribe

Creative Director 1/2010-Current

San Francisco, CA

- Supervised project collaborations with internationally recognized recording artists such as Shpongle and Ott, World Bodypaint Champions such as Trina Merry and Matteo Arfanotti and companies such as Google and Microsoft.
- Directed art projects for events such as Re: Creation San Francisco, Burning Man 2017, Hot Couture
- Raised over \$40,000 in private funds.
- Managed social media accounts totaling 20K in followers.

♥ ??? **♥**

127.0.0.1:5500/index.html 2/2